http://andrewsimports.com/shop/custom.aspx/policies/3/

Canada's #1 Pet Supplies Company
PO Box 1373 Grande Prairie AB T8V 4Z2
Ph# 780-513-3762
Fast, shipping within 24 hrs...
HomeAbout UsCategory ListPoliciesFeatured ItemsHow to SizeContact Us
Search ProductsItem #:Item Name:Description:Custom 1Custom 2Custom 3 Go
Sign-In
Order Status
Shopping Cart
Our Products
European craftsmanship with attention to detail is the hallmark of our entire product line. We select from only the most respected manufacturers to bring you the highest quality products available anywhere. Including eight completely differently designed muzzles with three different sizes in each. This full range of design and styles cover dogs from Chihuahua to Great Dane and everything in between.A full line of Leads, Leashes and Collars made from premium leather.100% Satisfaction guaranteed or your money back. Shipping and handling on single orders is Shipped at a flat rate per order
.All products shipped within 1 business day, See what our customers say
WHAT'S NEW!! Orders can be made also by fax or mail just follow the checkout feature.Thank you Andrew
Featured Items
Small Dogs Muzzle Size 2" length and 6" circ
# 10R0/0
This particular muzzle fits all breed with similar size snout. The
muzzle size is 2 inches in length and 6 inches in circumference.
Buy
Details
$31.99
In Stock!
German Shepherd Medium Size 4.5" length and 12.5" Circ
# 50R5
Perfect ventilation muzzle for medium size dogs #50R5 German
Shepherd
dogs. Also recommended for dogs (34 kg to 43kg).
Buy
Details
$31.99
In Stock!
Terms & Conditions
Shipping and Handling will be added to all orders. All invoices are due before shipment of orders. VISA , MASTERCARD and PayPal are accepted.
Online Purchases
All secure online purchases are administered by PayPal. For a full explanation of PayPal's terms and conditions please visit their web site at www.paypal.com.
Special and Custom Orders
Special orders require 50% deposit. Remainder due before delivery Allow 3-4 weeks. Shipping
All products will be shipped within 3 business days except special and custom orders.All orders will be shipped Canada Post Expedited or UPS/Purolator Ground unless specified by buyer.When order exceeds standard size and weight limits, "Common Carrier" will be used.
Return Policy
Product must be returned in 30 days and must be in resaleable condition.20% restocking fee will be applied on all returns. Shipping fees are not refundable.The products must be a normally stocked item (no special or custom orders).
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy:
Euro Imprts fully respects the privacy of every individual who visits our website. This privacy statement provides information on our data collection practices and of the ways in which the information may be used.
Personally-Identifiable Information
Euro Imprts receives personal information from website visitors only when such information is provided voluntarily, such as when our visitors register a company, request information, provide purchasing information for our online store, or send us e-mail.
When you provide personal information to Euro Imprts through our website, it will be used to fulfill your specific request. Euro Imprts may also use the information you provide to inform you about additional services and products offered by us.
Euro Imprts will never release, sell, or trade your personal information to third parties unless you have authorized us, or we are legally required to do so.
When you voluntarily offer any feedback, data, answers, questions, comments, suggestions, ideas or similar, Euro Imprts will treat that information as non-confidential and nonproprietary, and may utilize such information for informational, educational, or promotional purposes such as frequently asked questions lists or product/service testimonials.
Anonymous Information
The Euro Imprts website collects some generic information automatically; this is statistical information only. The data gathered lets Euro Imprts know when and how much traffic a web page gets. Internet IP addresses are also logged for security purposes.
This information does not include visitor identities or any personal data, and Euro Imprts will never combine this generic information with any personal information.
Euro Imprts Hosted Website and Third-Party Services
Additionally, the Euro Imprts website may contain links to unaffiliated third party sites where Euro Imprts cannot protect any information you may disclose. Euro Imprts recommends that you review the privacy policy statements of every site you visit.
Security Statement:
Our security measures begin as soon as you are required to enter any personal information into our website. This is completely automatic and requires no special action on your part. Once you click to register your company you are immediately in a secure environment, this occurs before you enter a single item of personal data. If you are simply purchasing a product from this web site you will be diverted to a secure environment as soon as you click the “buy” or "add to cart" button.
The secure environment is created by your browser and our digital certificate, when entering a secure area of the site your browser checks our secure certificate to ensure our web site is exactly as registered with the secure certificate. Once confirmation of the certificate is received, your computer and our server will begin communicating in secure mode, sending data back and forth in an encrypted format. The powerful encryption features standard in most browsers will ensure the security of the data that is passed between us. Our certificate has been issued by GoDaddy.
When we take payment for your order we communicate with PayPal, our payment service provider. The PayPal payment system uses a combination of established and innovative techniques to ensure the security and integrity of all sensitive data. Their internet facing web servers are certified by Verisign, this ensures no third parties can impersonate PayPal to obtain secure information.
If you have any concerns or questions about the security of this site or our systems please do not hesitate to contact us
Home   About Us   Category List   Policies   Featured Items   How to Size   Contact Us
Powered by NextStar, Inc
